She's too good to be true...and too real to be otherwise.
Galaxina is a comedy, science fiction film directed by William Sachs.
Galaxina is a lifelike, voluptuous android who is assigned to oversee the operations of an
intergalactic Space Police cruiser captained by incompetent Cornelius Butt.
When a mission requires the ship's crew to be placed in suspended animation for decades, Galaxina finds
herself alone for many years, developing emotions and falling in love with the ship's pilot, Thor.
Galaxina, played by Dorothy Stratten.
Sgt. Thor, played by Stephen Macht.
Capt. Cornelius Butt, played by Avery Schreiber.
Maurice, played by Lionel Mark Smith.
Buzz, played by J.D. Hinton.
Sam Wo, played by Tad Horino.
Galaxina is a 1980 American science fantasy-comedy film
written and directed by William Sachs.
Shot on a low budget, the film stars 1980 Playboy Playmate of the Year Dorothy
Stratten, who was murdered by her husband shortly after the film's release.
Besides its homages to and parodies of science fiction mainstays Star Trek (1966), Star
Wars (1977) and Alien (1979), this film also pokes fun at the Western genre.
It won the Audience Award at the 1983 Brussels
International Festival of Fantasy Film.
A film viewed by the characters in Galaxina is a clip from the 1960
Eastern bloc sci-fi film, First Spaceship on Venus.
The clip is used because First Spaceship on Venus was released
by Crown International Pictures in the U.S.
The film explores themes of android, spacecraft,
laser, space travel, cryogenics.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.